Burroughs Corporation Records. ElectroData Division Records, 1952-1979. Finding Aid.
University of Minnesota Libraries
- Engineering Technical Reports
  - ETR #5: Optical Character Recognition, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - ETR #6: Simplified Approach to Look-Ahead, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - ETR #7: Four Modes of Oscillation in Emitter Followers, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - ETR #8: B5000 System Reliability Analysis, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - ETR #9: Associative Techniques with Complementary Flip-Flops, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - ETR #10: Low Cost Ferrite Core Buffer Memory, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - ETR #11: B200/B5000 Magnetic Read/Write Circuits, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - ETR #12: Technical Progress During 1962, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - ETR #14: Integer Linear Programming Formulation of the Backboard Wiring Problem, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - ETR #19: Expanded Memory for the B200, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - ETR #20: Ferrite Memory Core Characteristics, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - ETR #22: Improvements in Transistorized RC Delay Circuits, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - ETR #23: Ferrite Core Memory Stack Transition, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - ETR #24: Information Theory, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - ETR #25: Magnetic Memory System Organizations, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - ETR #26: Analysis of Data Set Performance, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - ETR #27: Coding Theory, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - ETR #28: ASTM Standards for Ferrite Memory Devices, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - ETR #29: Silicon Oxide Charge and MOS Device Stability, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - ETR #30: Computer Aided Design of Semiconductor Circuits, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Engineering Technical Reports, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Engineering Technical Reports, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Duncan MacDonald Papers
  - 1751 and 1752 computers, 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - B200 Program, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - B200/B5000 Program, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - B2000, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
  - B2000 Product Proposal, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 6-8)
  - B2000 Program, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - B3000 Product Proposal, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 10-11)
  - B5000, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 12-13)
  - Bulk File Product Proposal, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Bulk File Study, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Design Automation Proposal and Status Report, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Disk File (Project 804), 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 17-20)
  - Engineering Budgets, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Engineering Project Forecast - Dept/ 6300, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Equipment Delivery Report (Group III), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Five Year Plans - Engineering Activity, 1967-1972 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Group III Engineering Program, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 25-26)
  - Historical Information on RE Projects, 1956-1959 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - New Products and Features Report, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - OCR Technical Reports, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Pasadena Engineering Presentation, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Personnel Activity Reports, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1954-1955 (Box 41)
  - 1956-1957 (Box 41)
- Miscellaneous Subject Files
  - B220 Operational Characteristics, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - B220 Report Generator I, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - B220 Technical Manual, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Bulk File Memory, 1963-1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Memory, 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Core Memory, 1963-1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Direct Access Mass Memory, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Disk Access Analysis, undated (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - Disk File, 1959-1970 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Disk Fixed Head Memory, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Document Log #8 (Meeting #48), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Document Log #9 (Meeting #49), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Document Log #10 (Meeting #50), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Document Log #11 (Meeting #51), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Document Log #12 (Meeting #52), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Document Log #13 (Meeting #53), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Document Log #14 (Meeting #54), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Document Log #15 (Meeting #55), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Document Log #17 (Meeting #57), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Document Log #18 (Meeting #58), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Document Log #19 (Meeting #59), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Document Log #21 (Meeting #61), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Document Log #22 (Meeting #62), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Document Log #24 (Meeting #64), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Document Log #25 (Meeting #65), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Document Log #26 (Meeting #66), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Document Log #27 (Meeting #67), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Document Log #28 (Meeting #68), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Document Log #29 (Meeting #69), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Document Log #30 (Meeting #70), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Document Log #31 (Meeting #71), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Document Log #32 (Meeting #72), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Document Log #33 (Meeting #73), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Document Log #34 (Meeting #74), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Dynabit Storage, undated (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - "I"nteger Documents, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Integrated Circuit Memory, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Large Data Storage Systems, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 39-40)
  - Magnetic Bubble Memory, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Magnetic Film Memory, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Magnetic Tape, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Magnetic Thin Film Analysis, 1960-1966 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Mass Memory, 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
  - Memory Comparisons, 1962-1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Memory Costs, 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Memory Device Characteristics, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Memory Disk Pack, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Memory Program Planning, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Memory Solid State, 1965-1972 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Memory Technologies, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Optical Memories, 1967-1970 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Optical Memory, 1965-1972 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Plated Wire Memory, 1969-1971 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Relational Memory, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Series G (G101) High Speed Printer, Operators Handbook, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Series G (G101) Parts Identification Manual, 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Technical Proposal for B5000, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Thermoplastic Recording, 1960, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Woven Screen memory (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - ElectroData News Releases, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - ElectroData News Releases, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - ElectroData News Releases, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 26-27)
  - ElectroData News Releases, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 28-29)
  - ElectroData News Releases, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 30-31)
  - ElectroData News Releases, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - ElectroData Merger: Agreement and Plan of Reorganization, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - ElectroData Merger: Plan of Merger and Memorandum of Agreement for Merger, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - ElectroData Merger: Proxy Statement for Agreement and Plan or Reorganization of ElectroData Corporation, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - ElectroData Merger: Purchase Agreement (with Allstate Insurance Company and Security First National Bank), 1956 (Box 40, Folder 36)